<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ella&#39;s World</title>
    <link>http://ellasworld.site/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ella&#39;s World</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 20:26:56 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://ellasworld.site/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Choir</title>
      <link>http://ellasworld.site/post/choir/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 20:26:56 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ellasworld.site/post/choir/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In my school we have a choir for years 3-6  and I’m in it. We sing songs for occasions such as the One Big Voice and the Children’s Singfest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the One Big Voice I’ll be singing&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I’ll Be There For You&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rain Song&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bumble Bee&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sunny Day&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Goodbye Beethoven&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On Top Of The World&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A Place In The Choir&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When The  Lights All Shine and Fight Song.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My favourite songs are Goodbye  Beethoven, Bumble Bee and When All The Lights All Shine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://onebigvoice.com.au/&#34;&gt;Here is a link to the One Big Voice website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speeches</title>
      <link>http://ellasworld.site/post/speeches/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 20:14:52 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ellasworld.site/post/speeches/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In my school we do speeches. Some times we get to choose our topic but most of the time our teacher chooses our topic. In the first weeks of the term, we have an easy time limit like 1-3 mins. But later in the term, we have a big time limit like 4-5 mins  which is pretty hard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My favourite speech so far is the life cycle of a star.
&lt;img src=&#34;http://ellasworld.site/img/lifecyclestar.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;
From &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.schoolsobservatory.org.uk/astro/stars/lifecycle&#34;&gt;http://www.schoolsobservatory.org.uk/astro/stars/lifecycle&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minecraft</title>
      <link>http://ellasworld.site/post/minecraft/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2016 10:46:39 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ellasworld.site/post/minecraft/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Minecraft is a game that you can play on your computer, playstation, xbox or a tablet. You can play survival mode which is were you start out with nothing at all. The other mode is creative were you have everything in minecraft.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In creative you can fly and the best part is that mobs don’t attack you. There are many skins and texture packs. Texture packs are things were you can change the colour and shape of most items for tablet version (minecraft PE).  There is the city texture pack and the plastic texture pack.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the city texture pack from a map I’ve downloaded (Kingdom of Fairheaven).
&lt;img src=&#34;http://ellasworld.site/img/city_texture_pack.png&#34; alt=&#34;city&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is me near Finn and Jake&amp;rsquo;s tree house (Land of Ooo) and this texture is the plastic.
&lt;img src=&#34;http://ellasworld.site/img/plastic_texture_pack.png&#34; alt=&#34;plastic&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If I had to rate this game this game out of ten I would give it a  9.5 out of 10.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cheesecake</title>
      <link>http://ellasworld.site/post/cheesecake/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2016 19:21:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ellasworld.site/post/cheesecake/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last weekend  I had a cheesecake at a friend’s house and my mum made it. It was delicious.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://ellasworld.site/img/eating_cheesecake.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Yum!&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are the ingredients:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul type=&#34;square&#34;&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;300 g wheat meal biscuits&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;500 g cream cheese&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;200 g castor sugar&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;1 tablespoon of corn flower&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;3 eggs&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;2 tablespoon of lemon juice&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;a few drops of pure vanilla and pinch of salt&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;2 cups of sour cream&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the whole recipe go to ”The Cook’s Companion” by Stephanie Alexander.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If I had to rate it out of ten, I would give it a nine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://ellasworld.site/img/cheesecake.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Stormy Day</title>
      <link>http://ellasworld.site/post/storm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2016 21:26:44 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ellasworld.site/post/storm/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;You will not believe what happened yesterday, it was so stormy! I didn&amp;rsquo;t go outside all day because of the storm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You may be wondering if I played netball?  Well I didn&amp;rsquo;t because of the weather.  The place where I play netball was deserted.  We didn&amp;rsquo;t realise until we got there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I saw some pictures of trees that had fallen onto houses and cars. It looked like all of the leaves from the mulberry tree were in our pool.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trampolining</title>
      <link>http://ellasworld.site/post/trampolining/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2016 17:34:38 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ellasworld.site/post/trampolining/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I used to de trampolining. In case you didn’t know what it is it is a sport where you do tricks on a trampoline. Like the straddle jump (splits in the air) or a flip (everyone knows what a flip is!). It’s so much fun but I had to stop because of netball as it clashes with trampolining so I can’t do it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://ellasworld.site/img/trampolining.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Me at trampolining&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Animal Jam</title>
      <link>http://ellasworld.site/post/animal_jam/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2016 21:24:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ellasworld.site/post/animal_jam/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Animal Jam is a game that you can play on a computer, Android tablet or an ipad. Animal Jam is a game that you play as an animal and the first animal you choose on Android is between a wolf, bunny or monkey. There a special types of places that only a certain animal can go to. There are mini games that you can play and you can  earn gems that you can use to decorate your den. There are also sapphires that you can use to buy new dens and new animals. If I had to rate this game out of 5 stars I would give it a 4 out of 5.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://ellasworld.site/img/animal_jam.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Animal Jam&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Netball</title>
      <link>http://ellasworld.site/post/netball/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2016 17:00:55 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ellasworld.site/post/netball/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I play netball on Saturday and the match starts at 8:40 am, that’s really early. I have to get there at 8:10 and I am in a big rush to get to netball. This Saturday Storm (our netball club) lost by one point, one point! We were so close for our first game.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://ellasworld.site/img/netball.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Me&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome</title>
      <link>http://ellasworld.site/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 23:28:02 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ellasworld.site/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi! I’m Ella I’m 9 years old and I like to play netball. My favourite animal is a porpoise and some   people don’t even know what a porpoise is! They are awesome. I live in Perth, Australia. I like to read and some books I like to read are Dork Diaries, Diary of a Wimpy Kid and Lulu Bell books. I have a pool in my backyard and I love to swim in summer and ride my bike in winter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://ellasworld.site/img/ella.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Me&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>