<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Games on Ella&#39;s World</title>
    <link>http://ellasworld.site/tags/games/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Games on Ella&#39;s World</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2016 10:46:39 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://ellasworld.site/tags/games/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Minecraft</title>
      <link>http://ellasworld.site/post/minecraft/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2016 10:46:39 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ellasworld.site/post/minecraft/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Minecraft is a game that you can play on your computer, playstation, xbox or a tablet. You can play survival mode which is were you start out with nothing at all. The other mode is creative were you have everything in minecraft.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In creative you can fly and the best part is that mobs don’t attack you. There are many skins and texture packs. Texture packs are things were you can change the colour and shape of most items for tablet version (minecraft PE).  There is the city texture pack and the plastic texture pack.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the city texture pack from a map I’ve downloaded (Kingdom of Fairheaven).
&lt;img src=&#34;http://ellasworld.site/img/city_texture_pack.png&#34; alt=&#34;city&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is me near Finn and Jake&amp;rsquo;s tree house (Land of Ooo) and this texture is the plastic.
&lt;img src=&#34;http://ellasworld.site/img/plastic_texture_pack.png&#34; alt=&#34;plastic&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If I had to rate this game this game out of ten I would give it a  9.5 out of 10.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Animal Jam</title>
      <link>http://ellasworld.site/post/animal_jam/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2016 21:24:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ellasworld.site/post/animal_jam/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Animal Jam is a game that you can play on a computer, Android tablet or an ipad. Animal Jam is a game that you play as an animal and the first animal you choose on Android is between a wolf, bunny or monkey. There a special types of places that only a certain animal can go to. There are mini games that you can play and you can  earn gems that you can use to decorate your den. There are also sapphires that you can use to buy new dens and new animals. If I had to rate this game out of 5 stars I would give it a 4 out of 5.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://ellasworld.site/img/animal_jam.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Animal Jam&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>